STU LABO This issue is brought to you from Strath Park Setoda, where the cherry blossoms are currently in full bloom!
What a beautiful day!
It's amazing.
But more importantly, it's still spring, Sora-san, even though the weather is like this!
It's still spring!
Last time I was here, you were dressed like this, so I thought I'd lift the ban.
Really? Okay.
And Riko Kudo and Azumi Okada will be with us today.
Pleased to meet you.
I've been watching the video for a long time, and I've seen it every time, so...
Today is my first time at Strath Park, so
I'm going to enjoy it as much as I can.
Awesome YouTuber!
This is my second time in Strathpark as STULABO.
Last time we created the STU flower area, toured the lemon grove, and had a great time at the glamping with Barrukie and 5 other YouTubers.
I enjoyed every single one of the 5 rounds of glamping and balky!
This time we will plant lemon trees!
It's hot out, so let's wait until it melts!
Let's plant right away!
I want to eat a squished lemon!
Oh my goodness!
I'm sure it's delicious.
Grate a lemon?
It's a radish.
Let's go for it.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Here we go. Lemon area.
Yay!
This is the person who will be cooperating with us this time, too!
Wow!
How much do we get?
Hi, I'm Hatta.
Welcome to the show.
Mr. Hatta.
We've been expecting you.
Good morning, Mr. Hatta.
You'll be working hard today.
I'll be working today.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
First meeting.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm fine with the steel frame.
Yeah.
Yeah
Wren.
Okay.
You forgot your idol.
Good luck!
Senior Agmin
Oh, I can do it!
I can do it!
I'm ready
Ren
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there
Almost there
gentle gentle gentle
go for it!
Wow!
I got it!
Everyone did it just fine.
What? I wonder if there are any fossils in there?
What's wrong with the sound?
Okay, let's plant this.
Woo...
This is a lemon tree.
Yes, sir.
That's great.
Oh, is this going to open up?
Spread it out?
A little at a time.
A little bit at a time from here.
Here.
Oh, there were 1,300 plants.
That's right.
Here we go!
Do this one by one.
Huh?
Hata-san, all by himself.
All of you, all of you!
That's great!
No, but it's great
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Finally, I'm going to give it a whiff.
Blow, blow, blow.
Let's see, let's have him hold the back a little bit while we harden it.
Oh, that's cute.
That's right.
It's a festival, right?
Let's all hold hands.
Ready?
Fumip fumip fumip
Blow, blow, blow!
No, I'm feeling it.
I don't like the diagram.I don't like the diagram.
Eh, that's enough.
I want to give it a name.
What? A name?
A name.
I want to name it.
I want to give you a name.
I want to give you a name
Younes.
You mean Yoness?
Jonés.
Why?
Lemon.
Oh, my God.
The cat's a bitch. It's hard to see.
Was it a stepper? Oh, my God.
Then you'll be in charge of the hairy ones, right? Please.
Oh, really? What about him? Still?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ready?
Fib, fib, fib, fib, fib, fib.
What? Wait a minute. What's that?
Eeeeee... so cute!
I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy
What? What is it? What is this?
This is lemon squash.
Wow! Amazing!
Stress bag. It says "Setoda" on it.
There's teal on it.
Special?
A special one.
Yay! Shall we have some?
Let's all make a toast together.
Let's do it! Let's have a toast!
Cheers! Cheers!
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Oh, my God, it's so sizzling.
It's good. It's good. It's good.
It's sweet, but it has a really clean aftertaste.
It's really refreshing.
It's not really spicy. It's really refreshing. It's really delicious.
Cancel it. Cancel it. Good luck.
It's perfect right now. It's spicy.
It's so good!
Let's have a commercial championship.
Suddenly? I'm in.
Okay, I'll start with Rireato.
Okay, let's get this camera.
Action!
Oh, I'm so tired today.
You'll do it for me? Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Mmmm!
It's delicious today, too.
This is the best. Setoda Stress Park.
Good, good, good.
Good, good, good, good!
Okay, next, Mr. Soran.
Okay, Mr. Soran.
All right, action!
I'm tired.
I'll take that.
No, thank you!
What the hell? It doesn't taste good.
No, thank you. I've had too much to drink.
Here we go.
Good, good, good.
Shall we continue with the commercial?
Seltzer banana.
Bitter sandwich. Delicious.
It's just Relena.
Just Relena. Just Relena. Just Relena.
Today is March 31st.
A word to the note
May you grow up soon!
Wow.
How's it doing?
Help me.
He's so cute.
Such a little guy.
You played with a turtle, didn't you?
Oh, my God.
Girls, girls, teach for children .
Oh, thank goodness!
Cat is so cute!
Japanese fairy
Neko wai yai!
Okay, it's done!
It's done!
[Hajime Shacho ending]
I hope it grows well.
I see.
I hope it grows up.
Oh! It looks good!
That's good! This one!
It stands out so much!
Nice! This is really good!Nice!!! Seriously, that's nice!
I want you to sit down! I really do!
Extra heat!
Hunter's getting bigger! The future!
We're in the mandarin orchard!
Yay! I'm so happy!
I'm going to get this tangerine tree and dig in the dirt,
I'll dig it up!
Oh! I'm so happy!
Then let's do it!
Let's do it!
Yes!
Then, let's ask Yamada-san to show us how to do it and let's go!
It's softer than before! This tree!
What? Why?
I don't know!
The leaves are tighter than before!
It's shinier and more beautiful than the last lemon!
I didn't notice it, but there was a bird in the lemon!
What! What's going on!
That's a great bird!
Are they on the leaves?
I didn't even notice!
Edami!
It's like a mala!
I'll eat a lemon or something later!
I don't eat lemons!
Oh, really? !
Because they are sour!
I eat oranges!
Is it okay if the oranges have needles on them?
If they have needles on them, yes!
So you want me to eat them?
Oh, yeah!
Like a sea urchin!
Watch out! Watch out!
Lemon picker!
Now, we'll do it the same way we did it before!
But it's got a lot of range!
It's so fluffy!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
He's got to hold it!
Oh, that's what I'm talking about!
Oh, no! It's a step road angle!
Oh, no! Suddenly, they're idolizing me!
The world of Ur-Air has been a very agitated one so far!
Unfortunately, it won't be,
Maybe in two years?
Two years!
Three years!
One year!
Here we go!
We've reworked our campaign and it's great. Don't miss the video download after we try this.
How much should it melt?
Dum-dum.
Rina, what do you think? Try it.
It's different.
It's very realistic.
It's so real.
I feel like I'm being crushed.
It's nice.
How do you like it when it's wet?
It's full of love.
It's very affectionate.
I'm sure they're sweet.
Let's go to Mogi. Every day.
I want to go to Mogi.
Let's go mogi mogi.